James A. Baker III Papers, 1957-2011 (bulk 1972-1992): Finding Aid MC197
Public Policy Papers
- Series 16: February 2011 Accession, 1957-2007 July 11; 22 boxes
  - Subseries 16A. Correspondence, 1993-1999; 8 boxes
    - 1993, 1 box (Box 266)
    - 1994, 1 box (Box 267)
    - 1995, 1 box (Box 268)
    - 1996, 1 box (Box 269)
    - 1997, 1 box (Box 270)
    - A-N, 1998; 1 box (Box 271)
    - O-Z, 1998; 1 box (Box 272)
    - 1999, 1 box (Box 273)
  - Subseries 16B. Events, 1993 January 7-1997 December 4; 8 boxes
    The files of events include the texts of speeches, email correspondence, programs, and other related documentation for events Baker attended.
    The materials in this collection have been maintained in the original order in which they were accessioned. Folder titles have also been maintained.
    - Commencement Address Sam Houston State University, 1993 May 15; 1 box (Box 274)
    - Reception in honor of Bakers Museum of Fine Arts, 1993 May 19; 1 box (Box 274)
    - Fundraiser Luncheon for KBH, 1993 May 24; 1 box (Box 274)
    - Commencement Address to Pinedale High School, 1993 May 29; 1 box (Box 274)
    - Trip to Europe & Moscow(B&B Opening), 1993 June 7 - 1993 June 16; 1 box (Box 274)
    - Lunch with B.McNair, JFWR at the Coronado Club, 1993 July 7; 1 box (Box 274)
    - Meeting with Jon Thompson of Exxon, 1993 July 7; 1 box (Box 274)
    - Reception for Leadership Committee, 1993 July 7; 1 box (Box 274)
    - Meeting with Malcolm Gillis (Talking points), 1993 July 8; 1 box (Box 274)
    - Lunch with John Cabiness Coronado Club, 1993 July 8; 1 box (Box 274)
    - Dinner for Jack Fields, 1993 July 8; 1 box (Box 274)
    - Lunch with B&B Summer Associates, 1993 July 9; 1 box (Box 274)
    - Partners Club at Houston Club, 1993 July 12; 1 box (Box 274)
    - Interview with Japanese Broadcasting Co, 1993 July 12; 1 box (Box 274)
    - Meeting with Perry Bass, 1993 July 13; 1 box (Box 274)
    - Mtg regarding Egypt at Enron, 1993 July 13; 1 box (Box 274)
    - 11:00 Phone call with Paul Laxalt, 1993 July 27; 1 box (Box 274)
    - 12:00 Lunch with Paul Howell, 1993 July 28; 1 box (Box 274)
    - 11:00 Meeting with Malcolm Gillis, 1993 July 28; 1 box (Box 274)
    - 3:00 Interview with Canadian Broadcasting, 1993 July 28; 1 box (Box 274)
    - Visit to Cooper Clinic, 1993 July 30; 1 box (Box 274)
    - Lunch with Bill Rugelshaus, 1993 August 3; 1 box (Box 274)
    - 2:00 Mtg; with Wasik Meshref, 1993 August 4; 1 box (Box 274)
    - Meeting with FM Iryani of Yemen, 1993 August 4; 1 box (Box 274)
    - Meeting with Oded Eran, 1993 August 9; 1 box (Box 274)
    - Mtg with Occ Petroleum & Gulf Resources at Enron, 1993 August 10; 1 box (Box 274)
    - VFW Nat Convention Dallas, Texas, 1993 August 23; 1 box (Box 274)
    - Brown Foud, Dinner HCC, 1993 September 12; 1 box (Box 274)
    - Reception with MH McLean & guests at HCC, 1993 September 26; 1 box (Box 274)
    - Palmer Golf Tournament, 1993 September 27; 1 box (Box 274)
    - Susan G. Baker at HBU, 1993 September 28; 1 box (Box 274)
    - Lunch with Al Hertzstein at Rice, 1993 September 29; 1 box (Box 274)
    - Meeting with Dr. Kawamoto B&B-Terry Thomas, 1993 September 29; 1 box (Box 274)
    - Baker Institute Lecture #2, 1993 September 30; 1 box (Box 274)
    - Meeting with Bolivia Pres. de Lasada, 1993 October 2; 1 box (Box 274)
    - UT's MD Anderson Cancer Center Convocation, 1993 October 1; 1 box (Box 274)
    - B&B Trip to Dallas, 1993 October 18 - 1993 October 19; 1 box (Box 274)
    - Susan G. Baker Remarks at Christ Episcopal Church, 1993 October 24; 1 box (Box 274)
    - B&B New Associate Orientation, 1993 January 7; 1 box (Box 274)
    - Salvation Army Luncheon, 1993 January 16; 1 box (Box 274)
    - Lunch with Aron Gordon; Lunch with D. de Menil, 1993 January 30-1993 December 1; 1 box (Box 274)
    - Meeting regarding Baker Institute (James A. Baker), 1993 December 2; 1 box (Box 274)
    - Goldman Sachs Conference New York City, 1993 December 3; 1 box (Box 274)
    - Remarks at Arthur Anderson Luncheon, 1993 December 15; 1 box (Box 274)
    - Meeting with Bill Walsh, Jr. Project Hope, 1994 January 11; 1 box (Box 274)
    - Interview with Y. Funabashi, 1994 January 11; 1 box (Box 274)
    - Interview with GMA, 1994 January 12; 1 box (Box 274)
    - TCB Board Meeting, 1994 January 12; 1 box (Box 274)
    - Interview with RTL, 1994 January 13; 1 box (Box 274)
    - Trip to San Tomas, 1994 January 14; 1 box (Box 274)
    - Courtesy Call with Dr. Klaus L. Aurisch, 1994 January 17; 1 box (Box 274)
    - Meeting with Mr. Salih Don Chapoton (B&B), 1994 January 18; 1 box (Box 274)
    - Food Marketing Institute Breakfast (Florida), 1994 January 19; 1 box (Box 274)
    - Baker Institute Lecture, 1994 January 21; 1 box (Box 274)
    - Meeting with E. Baird & Schlumberger Executives (New York City, New York), 1994 January 27; 1 box (Box 274)
    - Eleventh Annual Conference of Former Secretaries of State (Washington DC), 1994 January 27 - 1994 January 28; 1 box (Box 274)
    - "Grand Cross Award" Ceremony @ German Ambassador's Residence (Washington DC), 1994 January 30; 1 box (Box 274)
    - RNC Annual Gala DInner (Washington DC), 1994 February 3; 1 box (Box 274)
    - Hollywood Camp, 1994 February 7 - 1994 February 9; 1 box (Box 274)
    - Meeting at EDS Dallas, Texas, 1994 February 21; 1 box (Box 274)
    - Associated Republicans of Texas event Dallas, Texas, 1994 February 21; 1 box (Box 274)
    - Mtg with Dr. Dan Jones at B.I./TBD, 1994 February 22; 1 box (Box 274)
    - 10:30am Courtesy Call with Meir Romem, 1994 February 23; 1 box (Box 274)
    - Lunch with Housont Endowment/J. Blanton (Rice University), 1994 February 23; 1 box (Box 274)
    - International Livestock Congress, 1994 February 25; 1 box (Box 274)
    - Lincoln Day Dinner f/ New Mexico GOP, 1994 March 5; 1 box (Box 274)
    - Lunch with Lt. Gov Hobby & JFWR (Coronado), 1994 March 28; 1 box (Box 274)
    - B&B Meeting with TCI Denver, CO, 1994 March 29; 1 box (Box 274)
    - MCLE Presentation, 1994 March 30; 1 box (Box 274)
    - Trip to Princeton, 1994 April 19; 1 box (Box 274)
    - Remarks at Luncheon hosted by U. of H and Greater Houston Partnership, 1994 April 18; 1 box (Box 274)
    - B&B Partners Retreat, 1994 April 15; 1 box (Box 274)
    - Remarks at P. Owens event, 1994 May 18; 1 box (Box 274)
    - Annual Cuatro Caminos Conference Greater Austin Chamber of Commerce, 1994 May 19; 1 box (Box 274)
    - 12:00 Greater Houston Partnership Lunch (Four Seasons Hotel), 1994 May 16; 1 box (Box 274)
    - 2:00pm Meeting L. Clarkson (James A. Baker), 1994 May 18; 1 box (Box 274)
    - Rice Board Dinner Baker Institute Press Conference, 1994 May 19; 1 box (Box 274)
    - Remarks at the Houston Club, 1994 May 23; 1 box (Box 274)
    - 12:00pm Lunch with Gordon Cain, Paul Howell, and Ed Djerejian (Coronado Club), 1994 May 24; 1 box (Box 274)
    - 2:00pm Meeting with Allan King & Michael Rothchild (James A. Baker), 1994 May 25; 1 box (Box 274)
    - BBC Interview (Total Video Studio), 1994 May 25; 1 box (Box 274)
    - Trip to Savannah, Georgia, 1994 July 8; 1 box (Box 275)
    - Trip to Wyoming, 1994 July 12 - 1994 July 15; 1 box (Box 275)
    - 2:00pm Meeting with Thomas Beeby (James A. Baker), 1994 July 19; 1 box (Box 275)
    - Remarks at B&B Summer Associate Luncheon (38th Floor Conf Room), 1994 July 20; 1 box (Box 275)
    - CNN Interview 5:00pm WTVI Studios, 1994 July 25; 1 box (Box 275)
    - Event for Gov. Pete Wilson Newport Beach, CA, 1994 July 28; 1 box (Box 275)
    - Financial Times Interview, 1994 August 2; 1 box (Box 275)
    - Remarks at George W. Bush event, 1994 September 14; 1 box (Box 275)
    - Address to Reagan Forum, 1994 September 16; 1 box (Box 275)
    - Event for Rick Perry Ft. Worth, Texas, 1994 September 15; 1 box (Box 275)
    - Peninsula Speakers Series, 1994 October 13; 1 box (Box 275)
    - Event for Judge Don Wittig Houston, Texas, 1994 October 13; 1 box (Box 275)
    - Jim Inhofe for Senate Event Oklahoma City, OK, 1994 October 17; 1 box (Box 275)
    - Tex Lezar for Lt. Governor, 1994 October 18; 1 box (Box 275)
    - Senator Kay Bailey Hutchison for U.S. Senate, 1994 October 18; 1 box (Box 275)
    - Luncheon in honor of Francoise Djerejain 12:15pm at the Bayon Club [Susan G. Baker], 1994 October 21; 1 box (Box 275)
    - Justice Nathan Hecht for Texas Supreme Court, 1994 October 19; 1 box (Box 275)
    - Lunch for Nathan Hecht Houston, Texas, 1994 October 19; 1 box (Box 275)
    - Tejas Club Dinner Houston Country Club 7:00pm, 1994 October 27; 1 box (Box 275)
    - American Heart Association Power Breakfast, 1994 October 24; 1 box (Box 275)
    - Baker Institute Groundbreaking Ceremony, 1994 October 20; 1 box (Box 275)
    - Power Breakfast - '95 Heart Ball Ritz-Carlton, Houston, 1994 October 24; 1 box (Box 275)
    - Former Sec. States Conference, 1994 January 17; 1 box (Box 275)
    - 3:00pm Party for Marilyn & Doug Four Leaf Towers Party Room, 1994 January 20; 1 box (Box 275)
    - The Houston Forum, 1994 January 21; 1 box (Box 275)
    - Conference Call with Andy Ling & Townley Paton (James A. Baker) 5:00pm, 1994 January 21; 1 box (Box 275)
    - Meeting with Admiral Dan Murphy & Alex Copson (James A. Baker) 11:30 am, 1994 January 29; 1 box (Box 275)
    - Meeting with Mrs. Keightly & Judy Robinson [painting presentation], 1994 January 21; 1 box (Box 275)
    - Trinity University Event San Antonio, Texas, 1994 January 22; 1 box (Box 275)
    - American Jewish Committee Dinner, 1994 January 22; 1 box (Box 275)
    - Meeting with Dossett McCullough (James A. Baker) 10:00am, 1994 January 28; 1 box (Box 275)
    - GATT Speech (Washington DC), 1994 January 28; 1 box (Box 275)
    - Telephone call with DC High School Student (James A. Baker) 3:00pm, 1994 January 29; 1 box (Box 275)
    - George Bush Presidential Library Ceremonies, 1994 January 29; 1 box (Box 275)
    - Lehman Bros Event (New York, New York), 1994 December 5; 1 box (Box 275)
    - Hunting Trip with Sam Nunn (Ichauway, GA), 1994 December 16; 1 box (Box 275)
    - Meeting with Andy Ling & Townley Paton (Baker Institute), 1994 December 19; 1 box (Box 275)
    - Interview with Ennio Correto of Corriere, 1994 December 20; 1 box (Box 275)
    - Armstrong Ranch with Susan G. Baker, 1995 January 6-8; 1 box (Box 275)
    - Meeting with Ira Nishisato (James A. Baker), 1995 January 9; 1 box (Box 275)
    - Young President's Organization Houston, Texas, 1995 January 9; 1 box (Box 275)
    - Taylor Smith Group Town Forum Houston, Texas (Peter Roussel), 1995 January 10; 1 box (Box 275)
    - House Committee on Int'l Relations Hearing (DC), 1995 January 12; 1 box (Box 275)
    - Alfalfa Club Dinner (Washington DC), 1995 January 28; 1 box (Box 275)
    - Susan G. Baker: Texas Women's Retreat 1:00-3:00pm (J.W. Marriott), 1995 February 4; 1 box (Box 275)
    - Hunting Trip with Eberts & Cabanisses (San Chicago Camp), 1995 February 4-6; 1 box (Box 275)
    - Mtg with Harry Jones & Tim Brown 3:00pm (James A. Baker), 1995 February 8; 1 box (Box 275)
    - Smith Barney Energy Conference (Palm Springs, CA), 1995 February 9; 1 box (Box 275)
    - Mtg with Ray Velazquez 10:00am (James A. Baker), 1995 February 14; 1 box (Box 275)
    - Hunting Trip with Robert Day, 1995 February 17; 1 box (Box 275)
    - 8th Annual Economic Conference (Ritz-Carlton, Lisbon, Portugal), 1995 March 17; 1 box (Box 275)
    - Meeting with Boutros Boutros Ghali (New York), 1995 March 15; 1 box (Box 275)
    - Conference Call with Ken Lay, 1995 March 22; 1 box (Box 275)
    - 11:00am Telephone Interview (James A. Baker) with Amy Sorter Lifestyles Magazine, 1995 March 23; 1 box (Box 275)
    - Baker Institute USA-Mexico Conference (Houston, Texas), 1995 March 24; 1 box (Box 275)
    - Texas Union Lectureship in Student Leadership (Austin, Texas), 1995 March 28; 1 box (Box 275)
    - 3:00pm Phone Call with PM Bolger, 1995 March 30; 1 box (Box 275)
    - Foresight Interview Ms. Reiko Kinoshita (James A. Baker), 1995 March 30; 1 box (Box 275)
    - Marilyn & Doug's Wedding Houston, Texas, 1995 April 1; 1 box (Box 275)
    - Hunting with Chiles, Domenici & Nunn (Texas), 1995 April 7; 1 box (Box 275)
    - SA World Affairs Council San Antonio, Texas, 1995 April 11; 1 box (Box 275)
    - Meeting with Professor Herbert Parmet 2:00pm (James A. Baker), 1995 April 12; 1 box (Box 275)
    - Conference Call with Nassim Matar & Ed Djerejian, 1995 April 18; 1 box (Box 276)
    - A Celebration of Reading in honor of Barbara Bush Foundation for Family Literacy (Houston, Texas), 1995 April 22; 1 box (Box 276)
    - Enron Breakfast in honor of Turkish PM Cille (Ritz-Carlton Houston) 8:00pm, 1995 April 21; 1 box (Box 276)
    - Weekend in Hunt/Ingram, 1995 April 21-23; 1 box (Box 276)
    - Interview with Blythe Holbrooke UPLINK (James A. Baker) 3:00pm, 1995 April 25; 1 box (Box 276)
    - Trip to Domenica with Susan G. Baker, 1995 May 6; 1 box (Box 276)
    - Int'l Symposium / Foresight Magazine (Tokyo), 1995 May 15; 1 box (Box 276)
    - 10:30am Telephone Call with Ken Lay (James A. Baker), 1995 May 22; 1 box (Box 276)
    - 10:30am Telephone Interview with Gerald Posner, 1995 May 23; 1 box (Box 276)
    - 7:00pm Baker Institute Conference with Boutros Boutros-Ghali (Houston), 1995 May 25; 1 box (Box 276)
    - Middle East Peace Center conference (Washington DC), 1995 June 1; 1 box (Box 276)
    - World Meat Congress (Denver, CO), 1995 May 31; 1 box (Box 276)
    - Pennzoil Meeting (2:00pm), 1995 June 12; 1 box (Box 276)
    - B&B Luncheon with Summer Associates (Houston, Texas), 1995 June 28; 1 box (Box 276)
    - Meeting with Assad Jamal (James A. Baker), 1995 June 28; 1 box (Box 276)
    - Telephone Interviewith Y. Funabashi 1:30 am, 1995 June 30; 1 box (Box 276)
    - Meeting with Chief Minister Joshi 2:00pm, 1995 June 30; 1 box (Box 276)
    - Sanifill Luncheon (Coronado Club) 12:00pm, 1995 July 7; 1 box (Box 276)
    - The Grove (San Francisco, CA), 1995 July 28; 1 box (Box 276)
    - Aspen Institute Conference (Aspen, CO), 1995 August 2; 1 box (Box 276)
    - Mtg with J. MacWilliam & D. Respess 2:00pm (James A. Baker), 1995 August 22; 1 box (Box 276)
    - Interview with Satorn Suzuki with TV Asahi 2:30pm (James A. Baker), 1995 August 23; 1 box (Box 276)
    - Interviewith Ryosuke Harada (Nikkei) 10:00am (James A. Baker), 1995 August 30; 1 box (Box 276)
    - Rice Board Meeting (Lovett Hall) 8:30am Finance, 10:30am Board, 1995 September 12; 1 box (Box 276)
    - Interview with TV Tokyo (Tom Oki) 2:00pm (James A. Baker), 1995 September 12; 1 box (Box 276)
    - Phone Interview with Mr. Harada/Nikkei 2:45pm (James A. Baker) [we'll initiate the call], 1995 September 12; 1 box (Box 276)
    - Phone interview with Amanda Scoggins 11:00am (James A. Baker) 9/14/95, 1995 September 14; 1 box (Box 276)
    - Interview with Mr. Suzuki of TV Asabi 10:15am (James A. Baker), 1995 September 13; 1 box (Box 276)
    - Interview with H. Kawahara/Kyodo News 2:30pm (James A. Baker), 1995 September 13; 1 box (Box 276)
    - 10th Anniv. Plaza Accord / Bank of America (Plaza Hotel, New York), 1995 September 15; 1 box (Box 276)
    - Lewis & Clark College/Trans-Pacific Inst. Inaugural Lecture (Portland, OR), 1995 September 16; 1 box (Box 276)
    - Videotaping of Remarks in honor of Bushes 10:00am (James A. Baker) - Boy Scout Dinner 10:30, 1995 September 19; 1 box (Box 276)
    - Audiotaping of Book (Jay West Productions, Houston), 1995 September 20-22; 1 box (Box 276)
    - Timken Company Corporate Forum (Canton, OH), 1995 September 24; 1 box (Box 276)
    - Susan G. Baker: Friends of Nursing Luncheon St. Luke's Episcopal Hospital, 1995 September 28; 1 box (Box 276)
    - Annual Int'l Monetary Dinner Lehman Bros. (DC), 1995 October 8; 1 box (Box 276)
    - Interstate Natural Gas Assn. / 51st Annual Meeting (Amelia Island, FL), 1995 October 16; 1 box (Box 276)
    - Telephone Interview with Scott Hennen of KCNN-AM "Hot Talk" 10:10am, 1995 October 17; 1 box (Box 276)
    - Booksigning at Rice University 5:00-6:30pm (Cohen House), 1995 October 17; 1 box (Box 276)
    - Flemings /WSB event (New York), 1995 October 19; 1 box (Box 276)
    - Aspen Conference (Japan), 1995 October 24; 1 box (Box 276)
    - Boy Scout Council Dinner in honor of Bushes (James A. Baker name lent only), 1995 October 30; 1 box (Box 276)
    - CARE dinner (Houston), 1995 January 8; 1 box (Box 276)
    - Taping for Steve Smith Sunday (James A. Baker) 2:00pm, 1995 January 9; 1 box (Box 276)
    - Booksigning at Brazos Bookstore 6:00-7:30pm, 1995 January 9; 1 box (Box 276)
    - Telephone Interview with Steve Beckner 10:00 (we'll inititate the call), 1995 January 10; 1 box (Box 276)
    - Interview with Thomas Ellis/Greek TV 2:00pm (James A. Baker), 1995 January 10; 1 box (Box 276)
    - UT Texas-Ex Event in honor of Tom Loeffler Evening (San Antonio, Texas), 1995 January 10; 1 box (Box 276)
    - Baker Institute Annual Conference, 1995 January 13; 1 box (Box 276)
    - Goodall Reception / McNair Reception 6:00pm James A. Baker & Susan G. Baker to drop by both, 1995 January 14; 1 box (Box 276)
    - Intervew with A. Petrie of CBC Newsworld 9:00am (KHOU-TV Studios), 1995 January 15; 1 box (Box 276)
    - World Affairs Council of Philadelphia, 1995 January 16; 1 box (Box 276)
    - Institutional Investors' Roundtable (Scottsdale, AZ), 1995 January 17; 1 box (Box 276)
    - Lunch f/ Preston Moore's Golf Tourny 11:00am (Memorial Park) Susan G. Baker attending, too, 1995 January 21; 1 box (Box 276)
    - Phone interview with Gene Burns of WKOX-AM in Boston 9:15am CST (James A. Baker), 1995 January 21; 1 box (Box 276)
    - Mtg with Lauren & Benito Herrera (James A. Baker) 11:00am, 1995 January 22; 1 box (Box 276)
    - Conference Call with d. Cheney & John Smale 3:30pm, 1995 January 27; 1 box (Box 276)
    - Teleconference with George Russell 10:00am CST (James A. Baker), 1995 January 28; 1 box (Box 276)
    - Telephone interview with Golam Arshad 3:00pm (James A. Baker), 1995 January 28; 1 box (Box 276)
    - Interview with T. Kakuma with Sapio 2:00pm, 1995 January 28; 1 box (Box 276)
    - Lunch EWB, G. Jennings - Max Lukens & Jin Woods of EDS (TBD: Coronado), 1995 December 18; 1 box (Box 276)
    - Travel to UK, 1995 December; 1 box (Box 276)
    - UK Hunting Trip, 1995 December; 1 box (Box 276)
    - Interview with Anthony Seldon (James A. Baker) 8:45am Re: John Major, 1995 December 19; 1 box (Box 276)
    - Phone interview with Patrick Groomes (10:00am - James A. Baker), 1995 December 19; 1 box (Box 276)
    - Meeting with Andrew Cummins (James A. Baker) 2:00pm, 1995 December 19; 1 box (Box 276)
    - Interview with Toru Hata of Tokyo Shinbun 10:00am (James A. Baker), 1995 December 20; 1 box (Box 276)
    - Meeting with Bill Barr (James A. Baker) 3:00pm, 1995 December 20; 1 box (Box 276)
    - Bill Bruce luncheon at HCC (Library) 12:00pm, 1995 December 24; 1 box (Box 276)
    - Lunch with E. Djerejian & H. Chavanne (12:00pm - location TBD), 1996 January 3; 1 box (Box 277)
    - Telephone Interview with Ted Clark of NPR 10:00am (James A. Baker) T. Clark to initiate the call, 1996 January 11; 1 box (Box 277)
    - Weekend with Amstrongs, 1996 January 12; 1 box (Box 277)
    - Meeting with H. Owada & CG Sasaki 10:30am (James A. Baker), 1996 January 19; 1 box (Box 277)
    - Reception for Caroline Baker (TBD) Houston, Texas, 1996 January 17; 1 box (Box 277)
    - Meeting with Stacy Eastland (James A. Baker) 9:00am, 1996 January 1; 1 box (Box 277)
    - Interview with C. Adam KTRK-TV (James A. Baker) 2:30pm Re: Barbara Jordan, 1996 January 17; 1 box (Box 277)
    - Meeting with Sen. Kay Bailey Hutchinson 3:30pm (James A. Baker), 1996 January 19; 1 box (Box 277)
    - New Horizons '96 Conference (Orlando, FL), 1996 February 27; 1 box (Box 277)
    - Meeting with H. Alverson & W. Bayazid 2:00pm (James A. Baker), 1996 January 19; 1 box (Box 277)
    - Hunting with The Djerejians (Kenedy County, Texas), 1996 January 22; 1 box (Box 277)
    - Phone Call with General Barak (TBD) 9:30am CST - GB to inititate call, 1996 January 24; 1 box (Box 277)
    - Meeting with Bob Baker regarding Conrail 1:00pm (James A. Baker), 1996 January 25; 1 box (Box 277)
    - Phone Call with Hugh O'Brien (TBD) 10:30am CST - HO to initiate call, 1996 January 24; 1 box (Box 277)
    - Taping for Houston Endow. Jesse H. Jones Documentary (10:00am - James A. Baker), 1996 February 8; 1 box (Box 277)
    - Rice Board Meeting / Strategid Planning 3:00-5:00pm (Houston), 1996 February 8; 1 box (Box 277)
    - Lunch with EPD & Nancy Allen 12:00pm (Cohen House), 1996 February 8; 1 box (Box 277)
    - China in Asia Conference / Baker Institute Houston, Texas, 1996 February 9-10; 1 box (Box 277)
    - Hunting Trip with S. Rush & D. Baker, 1996 February 10-12; 1 box (Box 277)
    - Interview with Kuwait TV Wafik Ramadan (James A. Baker), 1996 February 15; 1 box (Box 277)
    - Hunting Trip with Johnston, Baker & Bruce (Sands Souci), 1996 February 19; 1 box (Box 277)
    - Meeting with Lee Hogan of HI Energy 11:00am (James A. Baker), 1996 February 27; 1 box (Box 277)
    - Interview B. Edwards with Morning Edition 10:00am (James A. Baker) National Public Radio, 1996 February 27; 1 box (Box 277)
    - Fishing Trip with President Bush (Freeport, Texas), 1996 March 4; 1 box (Box 277)
    - Meeting with Dr. H. Lehmann-Gruber 11:00am (James A. Baker), 1996 March 5; 1 box (Box 277)
    - Interview with R. Burdy f/Deutsche Welle 10:00am (James A. Baker), 1996 March 5; 1 box (Box 277)
    - Interview with C. Bruck of The New Yorker 2:00pm (James A. Baker), 1996 March 5; 1 box (Box 277)
    - Carter Center (Atlanta, GA), 1996 March 9-10; 1 box (Box 277)
    - Interview with Yomiuri Shimbun (Mr. Nosaka) 3:00pm (James A. Baker), 1996 March 7; 1 box (Box 277)
    - EDS Board meeting Washington DC, 1996 March 11; 1 box (Box 277)
    - Meeting with Rajai Khoury (James A. Baker), 1996 March 12; 1 box (Box 277)
    - Phone calls with RBS, TK & Frank Lavin (3:30pm, 4:00pm CST), 1996 March 12; 1 box (Box 277)
    - Rice Board of Governors' Dinner (O'Connor House) with Susan G. Baker, 1996 March 12; 1 box (Box 277)
    - Mtg with Prof. John Sloan 10:00am (James A. Baker), 1996 March 12; 1 box (Box 277)
    - Florida Leadership Prayer Breakfast TBD am (Tallahassee, FL), 1996 March 14; 1 box (Box 277)
    - Meeting with Bill Slusser & Others 10:00am (James A. Baker) re: Exxon, 1996 March 18; 1 box (Box 277)
    - TI Check Presentation (Rice) 11:00am - lunch following, 1996 March 19; 1 box (Box 277)
    - Breakfast Club Address (ROCC) 7:15am, 1996 March 20; 1 box (Box 277)
    - Meeting with Eric Yates 9:15 (James A. Baker), 1996 March 20; 1 box (Box 277)
    - Shell Oil Company Dinner 7:00pm (Four Seasons Hotel, Houston), 1996 March 20; 1 box (Box 277)
    - Dinner & Meeting with R. Vyakhirev (B&B - Dallas, Texas), 1996 March 20-21; 1 box (Box 277)
    - Phone Interview with M. Abdularahim 10:00am (James A. Baker), 1996 March 21; 1 box (Box 277)
    - PHH Network Services (Palm Desert, CA), 1996 March 23; 1 box (Box 277)
    - RNC Presidential Trust pm (Phoenix, AZ), 1996 March 26; 1 box (Box 277)
    - Boston Co. Asset Mgmt Client Conference (Tucson, AZ), 1996 March 26; 1 box (Box 277)
    - DePelchin Children's Home Gala in honor of James A. Baker & Susan G. Baker (Houston), 1996 April 2; 1 box (Box 277)
    - Phone call with Amb. Pashayev /Azerb. 10:00am (James A. Baker), 1996 April 3; 1 box (Box 277)
    - Golf with EWB, GB & Max Lukens (am) Houston Country Club, 1996 April 4; 1 box (Box 277)
    - Telephone Interview with Muriel Dobbin 3:00pm CST (James A. Baker), 1996 April 4; 1 box (Box 277)
    - Republicans Abroad Taping (James A. Baker) 3:00pm, 1996 April 8; 1 box (Box 277)
    - Rice Board Meeting (Duncan Residence) 4:00pm (9 Briarwood Court), 1996 April 8; 1 box (Box 277)
    - Kazakhstan trip; Singapore/Hong Kong/Germany/Azerbaijan trip, 1996 April 10; 1 box (Box 277)